http://www.celebitchy.com/privacy_policy/

Privacy, Data Protection and Cookie Policy
What information do we collect?
When commenting on our site you are asked to enter a name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously if you do not comment.
We collect information from you when you comment on our site.
This includes the contents of your comments, the name you provide (which does not have to be your own name), your IP address and the email address and website you provide, if applicable.
Your comments, IP address and the email and website you include with a comment are stored indefinitely in our database. The email address you provide and your IP address are not visible to anyone outside our administrative team. The contents of your comments and the name, website and avatar you use to comment (if applicable) are visible on our site, accessible to the public and searchable.
We also work with Google Analytics and Quantast to track user data on an aggregate basis. Your individual data is protected under the privacy protection and data retention policies of each company. You can learn more at Google Analytics and Quantast.
For California Residents
California law gives residents the right to opt out of the “sale” of their personal information to third parties, including for advertising purposes. Under California law, the sharing of your information with a service provider for advertising purposes could be considered a “sale.” To opt out of the sharing of your information for advertising information, click the opt out link provided in the footer of this page. You also have the right to request from us the categories of personal information that we have shared and the categories of third parties to whom the information was provided. To make such a request, please contact us at info@adthrive.com. To be clear we do not share your name, contact information, or any other sensitive information with third parties, and the categories of third parties that we share information with for advertising purposes are supply side platforms, programmatic advertising exchanges, and demand side platforms.
Obtaining and requesting deletion of your personal data
You can request deletion of specific comments by using the “Report This Comment As Spam or Abuse” link located under the comment you wish to delete. First verify the image as requested on the form. In the commenting box include the email address you used to comment on the site and write something like “I used the email xxx to comment. This is my comment and I would like it deleted.”
If you are an EU citizen and would like a digital copy and/or deletion of some or all of the comments you have made on our site, please email us at: info@celebitchy.com or cbcomments@gmail.com
In your e-mail to us, please use the subject line: GDPR data request.
In order to find your information we will need one or more of the following:
1. The email address you used to comment on our site
If you provided a non-working or fake email address we can still find your comments and send them to the email of your choice. (This is also not a violation of our comment policy as long as you consistently used the same username.) However if you provided more than one email address, or if you forgot the email you used, we cannot guarantee we will be able to locate your comments.
2. The username you used to comment on our site
If you used several usernames this is a violation of our commenting policy and a bannable offense. However that does not necessarily mean that you cannot be given a copy of all the comments you have made on the site. You have the right to obtain your comments and have them deleted, it just depends if we can find them with the information you provide. Usernames which are common words or frequently used names may take more time to locate than unique usernames. Please note that if you used a common name or word for your username we will need additional information before providing you with this data and verify that it is you.
3. The IP address of the computer or device you last used to comment on our site
IP addresses change frequently and this may be difficult to obtain. You can visit the site What is My IP Address to get your IP.
If we can find your comments with the information you provide in your email to us, we can email you a copy of them. You have the right to request that all your comments be deleted or that specific comments be deleted.
Please note that providing a digital copy of your comments and/or deleting comments at your request does not mean that you will be granted access to comment or that your comments will not be reviewed. Please see our comment policy for more information.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you chose to comment.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors.
These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here.
We use third-party advertising companies, including Google adsense, to serve the ads displayed on our website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email or phone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see http://optout.networkadvertising.org
The use of cookies enables them to serve ads to users based on their visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA
(Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website,
products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Cookie and Privacy Policy
If we decide to change
our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on November 10, 2020.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
